Contact

+972545524589 (Mobile) lazebnik.teddy@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/teddy-lazebnik-b159a88a (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Programming
Algorithms
Project Management

Languages

English (Full Professional)
Hebrew (Native or Bilingual)
Russian (Full Professional)

Certifications

Become a Data Scientist

AR\VR development in Unity and C#

Honors-Awards

Outstanding Ramat - Gan's student Student's Honor First place Barinkaton winner

Publications

A stable algorithm for numerical matrix exponent
Return on Data
Quadratic Hamiltonian

Teddy Lazebnik

Co-Founder & Algorithm Developer at dnc-algo

Summary

Algorithms and Al developer in the fields of Numerical Calculation, Data analysis, and NLP, (Computer Vision); flexible and project-oriented team player with leadership skills. A proven record in system architecture, production-ready algorithms, and working with clients. Always try to develop creative and effective solutions for a better match between customer needs and company priorities. Highly motivated, with CAN DO approach and open to learning.

Managing partner in DnC-algo, an outsourcing company specialized in machine learning (deep learning), mathematical modeling, cloud architecture, and data-driven solutions.

You can take a look on my open source projects:

- 1. Lightweight JS pathfinding genetic programming: https:// bitbucket.org/teddy_lazebnik/js-path-finding-genetic-programming/ src/master/
- 2. Hebrew associative word distance calculator: https://bitbucket.org/teddy_lazebnik/hebrew-associative-word-calculator/src/master/
- 3. A simple run-time class generator for python class: https://bitbucket.org/teddy_lazebnik/python-class-generator/src/master/
- 4. A simple 3d infinity run game takes place in space: https://github.com/ArielA147/Space-temple-run
- 5. An extension of Knn and Kmeans algorithms: https://bitbucket.org/teddy_lazebnik/knn_over_time/src/master/
- 6. A mobile game in Unity where you build a tower from blocks and enemies trying to break it down: https://bitbucket.org/teddy_lazebnik/babylonian-revenge-mobile-game/src/master/
- 7. Academic Papers PDF to Text using classical computer vision (Java): https://bitbucket.org/galk-opensource/paper-pdf-text-extractor/src/master/
- 8. PubMed and arXiv full paper downloader (Java): https:// bitbucket.org/galk-opensource/pubmed-arxiv-paper-downloader/src/ master/

Experience

dnc-algo Co-Founder & Algorithm Developer April 2019 - Present

Ramat Gan Area, Israel

dnc-algo is an outsourcing company specialized in machine learning (deep learning), mathematical modeling, Cloud architecture, and data-driven solutions.

The company is based on both Israeli and Russian teams of professionals with both academic and market experience in algorithmic solutions in different scales.

Responsible for project management, algorithm development, software architecture, and business development.

Bar-Ilan University
Research And Teaching Assistant
October 2018 - Present
Ramat Gan Area, Israel

Assistant teacher of the courses:

2019 -> P.D.E and Introduction to linear mathematical optimization.2020 ->Numerical Analysis 1 and Introduction to linear mathematical optimization.

Taranis

Al Reseacher October 2018 - June 2019 (9 months) Tel Aviv Area, Israel

- * Research and developing of deep learning solutions (computer vision) in the area of agriculture using Python, TensorFlow.
- * Cloud architecture (Google cloud) for the Al part of the system, facing optimizing of performance and minimization of costs.
- * End to end solution design and developing using traditional ML, DL, and traditional computer vision and graph theory algorithms together.

ViaeAi
Algorithm Developer
August 2017 - September 2018 (1 year 2 months)

Tel Aviv Area, Israel

* Developing from scratch end2end solution for chatbots based on scripts and machine learning.

System design, training ML algorithms (JAVA & MATLAB), back-end web development (JAVA).

- * Design and build a Russian NLP engine (java) using linguistics expert and English-Russian transcripts.
- * Leading a team of 8 developers
- * Finished after the company has been sold

IDF

Algorithm Developer February 2017 - July 2017 (6 months)

Tel Aviv Area, Israel

Developing automatic data analysis tools (C#) for Human Resource Management process

ORT Israel, Technology & Science Educational Network Mathematics and Programming Teacher September 2014 - February 2017 (2 years 6 months)

Ramat Gan Area, Israel

Teaching math and computer science class (C# Programming, data structures, and algorithms).

In addition, writing a study program for youth gifted in mathematics.

WingSourcing
Co Founder & Algorithm developer
June 2016 - January 2017 (8 months)
Tel Aviv Area, Israel

- * Collaborations which third-party companies for joint technological developments, client's projects and financial management.
- * Building project plans according to users' will and professionals recommendations.

In addition, build the software architecture and develop the unique algorithms of each project.

- * Leading the development process with 4 developers.
- * Finished after the company has been sold

Ring Ad Ring
PM & algorithms
May 2014 - August 2016 (2 years 4 months)
Tel Aviv

A proven record of achievements in designing and implementing complicated systems using Object Oriented methodologies and Design Patterns.

Responsible for providing technical solutions, effort estimations, commitments.

Lead the improvement of product Quality & Performance by inserting automatic testing into release process.

Leading the development process with 5 developers.

FreeLance Developer 2012 - June 2016 (4 years)

Tel Aviv Area, Israel

Developed the following software for clients as a freelancer: (Usually with other professionals)

- 1. Web sites based on HTML, CSS, JS, and PHP (MySql as DBMS)
- 2. Android applications (team leader and JAVA programming)
- 3. BI system for a restaurant (PHP implementation)
- 4. Image analyzation of moles' cancer (JAVA implementation)
- 5. Machine Learning of fractal matrices (C# implementation on Windows Forms)
- 6. Symbolic Quadric Hamiltonian Solver for n=1,2 (C implementation)
- 7. Main locations on map calculator using user-based information (C# implementation)

Education

Bar-Ilan University

Doctor of Philosophy (Ph.D.), Mathematics and Computer Science · (2018 - 2022)

Bar-Ilan University

Master of Science (M.Sc.), Applied Mathematics · (2016 - 2018)

Bar-Ilan University

Bachelor of Science (B.Sc.), Applied mathematics and Computer Science · (2013 - 2016)